Wait, you yesterday...
...wore these pants, right?
Yeah, didn't they get washed?
Darn it, darn it, darn it.
You forgot to empty the pockets!
I haven't done laundry in over ten years!
Try it, see if it still... still works.
No, no.
This won't do, won't do.
Don't turn it on yet, don't put the battery in.
You, uh...
...dry it with a hairdryer first.
Alright.
Dry it first.
Weiguo.
Let me tell you.
You really have a way.
Sis, Big Bro isn't being stubborn anymore.
He keeps asking every day when you're coming back.
So when should I go back?
Your big brother is so careless.
I've been away for days now.
I don't know how things are at home.
Don't worry, hold out a few more days.
Besides, I'm here.
Don't you worry.
Okay, I'll listen to you then.
Hanging up now.
Auntie.
Tongtong.
Haven't seen you in so long, I've missed you.
Where are you?
You're so sweet, remembering your auntie.
So, have you seen Feifei lately?
Feifei? Feifei's doing just fine.
Where are you? I'll come find you.
Okay, good. Let's do that.
I grew up in this very alleyway.
I saw it last time I was here.
Dad.
Teacher Xiatian is here.
Teacher Xiatian.
Master Wang, something on your mind?
No.
Just thinking about the shop's business.
What a coincidence.
I came today...
...to formally discuss a partnership with you.
Oh, right. Okay, let's go inside and talk.
Actually, here's an idea.
My third son...
...he's more skilled in this area.
You two should have a chat.
Feifei, quick.
Take Teacher Xiatian inside.
Get some water, pour some tea.
Please, come inside, come inside.
This way, please, this way.
Mind the step.
Where are you going?
I'm going to pick up your sister-in-law.
My life...
...can't keep being such a mess.
Fine, go find her then.
Be careful.
Dad, I called Jing'er...
...but she hasn't been answering.
Is, is she with you?
She left the day before yesterday.
What? Went where?
No, wait, hold on.
Alright, look, I'm coming over right now.
You wait for me at home.
What do you mean 'left'? Gone?
Auntie.
Have a seat.
Wow.
You look so beautiful, Auntie.
Completely different from before.
Well, a few days away for a makeover.
Really, it's a whole new you.
What would you like to drink?
An Americano.
Waiter, an Americano here, please.
Coming right up.
Does it look good?
Yes, very pretty.
So, Auntie, planning to go back?
Been away for several days.
Time to go back.
About time.
So, has Uncle Wang reflected enough?
He should have by now.
You know, Tongtong...
...when I was young...
...I'd often meet up with my girlfriends.
Have a coffee date for afternoon tea.
Go shopping, buy things.
What about my uncle then?
What did he like to do?
Him?
Back then, he was chasing me.
Just riding that beat-up motorcycle of his.
Wherever I went, he'd just hang around.
So annoying.
Such a show-off.
Yeah.
Later, I stopped drinking coffee too.
Not because the coffee wasn't good.
Mainly because your Uncle Wang has a weak stomach.
So I...
...switched to drinking tea with him.
Auntie, you sacrificed a lot for Uncle Wang.
I wouldn't call it sacrifice.
After your Uncle Wang married me...
...he stopped playing in his band.
Stopped riding his motorcycle.
I never forced him.
When we were dating...
...we'd also call each other 'darling' this and 'darling' that.
Always on our lips.
But I don't know when it started...
...that 'darling' became 'Lao Wang' and 'Jing'er'.
I've been thinking these past few days.
When it comes to living a life together...
...it really has to be this 'Lao Wang' and 'Jing'er'.
Right?
When two people are together...
...you can't just think about yourself.
You have to consider the other person too.
See?
He didn't force me...
...to not drink coffee.
And later, he didn't insist on living...
...his carefree life.
Right?
How's Feifei? He's fine.
Feifei is doing well.
Thank you.
Thanks.
But they've all been asking me about how you are.
Okay, hearing you say that, I understand now.
Come back with me.
What do you say?
Let's go back.
I'm happy for you, Auntie.
This is Manager Zhou from the branch's HR department.
She's here specifically about your promotion.
Manager Zhou, this is Lao Tong.
Hello, hello, Manager Zhou.
Thank you for making the trip.
You look quite like the photo.
Yes, yes.
Photo?
The person in this photo is you, correct?
It's me, but...
Where did you get this photo?
We received an anonymous tip-off letter.
It accuses you of using improper methods
to acquire clients and illegally solicit deposits.
Impossible! No way!
That's not true, not true at all!
Let me explain this to you...
Ask Vice President Liu!
No matter how you explain it,
this photo is real, isn't it?
Yes, it's real.
Once this photo gets out
and falls into the hands of people with ulterior motives
who spin it a certain way,
the negative impact on our bank
would be immense.
Yes, it would definitely cause a bad... impact.
But that's not what happened!
Vice President Liu knows the whole story! You...
Vice President Liu, could you... Manager Zhou...
Could you... say something?
Vice President Liu?
Alright, you can leave now.
The leadership's decision
will be communicated to you later.
But... but...
Vice President Liu, you...
Please explain to her...
It's not like that!
You, don't get too anxious.
We will conduct further verification.
So you're still verifying, right?
Correct.
Please see the truth! See the truth!
This...
really needs to be clarified.
Don't worry, don't worry.
Please close the door for me.
Okay.
Door's closed.
Alright, let's talk about your issues.
Manager Zhou, he did this mess privately.
I... I had no knowledge of it at all!
No knowledge?
How can you be a leader if you were unaware?
The tip-off letter we received
tells a different story.
It says you not only knew about it,
but you also instructed Tong Qiu to do it proactively.
Slander!
Pure slander!
And your problems go far beyond this.
The letter also states
that you have long ignored actual conditions
to set excessively high KPI targets,
causing widespread complaints among frontline staff.
Furthermore,
you approved loans in violation of regulations
and accepted bribes privately.
After deliberation by the branch's senior leadership,
you are relieved of all your duties
pending an internal investigation.
Subsequently, we may refer the case to the public security organs
to pursue criminal liability.
You are expected to cooperate at that time.
Why are you back alone?
Your sister-in-law is missing.
What?
My father-in-law told me
that a couple of days ago,
she went out with a girlfriend to have fun.
Then I texted her, called her...
and she just stopped responding.
When was the last time you contacted her?
This morning.
This morning I asked her,
"When are you coming back?"
Then she said she'd be back in a couple of days.
After that, she went off the grid.
That shouldn't be.
Why is she improvising?
What do you mean, improvising?
I told her
to go stay at her parents' place for a couple of days.
But I didn't tell her to go out and have fun.
Wait, you told her to stay at her parents' for two days?
What's your deal? What do you mean?
Big brother, to tell you the truth,
she's angry with you.
Angry with me? What did I do to make her angry?
Think about it yourself.
What have you been doing lately?
What have I been doing?
Think about it.
I, I, I...
I've just been busy in the kitchen, right?
Then I work on my self-media account.
Right?
And then I hang out with you guys,
we chat together, right?
And also, I...
the collaboration I'm discussing with that Teacher Xiatian.
Anything else?
No, that's about it.
See? You listed so many things,
and not a single one involves sister-in-law.
Haven't you been neglecting her?
No, hasn't it always been like this?
How is that neglecting her?
You and Feifei,
working on that self-media account,
you think sister-in-law doesn't understand it,
so you have nothing to talk about with her.
And also,
I think maybe you're
paying too much attention to that Teacher Xiatian.
No, with Teacher Xiatian, we...
Is she jealous about that?
It's not about jealousy.
Then think again.
During this time sister-in-law has been gone,
how have you been feeling?
What have I been feeling?
I just feel like everything, at home and at the shop,
is all messed up, I tell you.
Usually,
you feel like sister-in-law doesn't do much,
but once she's gone,
neither home nor the shop runs smoothly, right?
Big brother, honestly,
sister-in-law has done so much for you,
but you never make her feel seen.
Tell me, how could she not be angry?
Is it sister-in-law?
What did she send?
I'm out having fun.
Don't keep calling me for no reason.
Isn't that infuriating?
And even sent a photo over.
Looks pretty happy.
Big brother, just relax.
Sis-in-law is a grown woman.
It's fine if she goes out for a couple days.
What do you mean 'fine'?
Let me talk to her.
Jing'er?
Well, if nothing's wrong, come back early.
Let's have a proper talk, okay?
Alright, big brother.
Don't worry.
Sis-in-law is a grown woman.
Playing for two days shouldn't be a problem.
Besides, she already sent a photo.
Don't worry about it.
Show her a little more concern.
No, the question is when is she coming back?
I don't know that.
How about this, send her a message.
See if she replies.
Just call her directly, give it a try.
She answered.
Hello? Sis-in-law?
Did you change your phone?
It's me, Weiguo.
Where are you?
In Sanya, right?
Okay, alright, alright, okay.
No, don't worry, I won't tell big brother.
No, what are you doing in Sanya?
Okay, that's it then.
Hello?
You're the one who took sis-in-law, right?
So clever.
What's the reason?
She's been trapped in her own little world for too long.
Wants to rebel a little.
But doesn't dare go too far.
I'm just lending her a little courage.
So how far can she go?
Don't know. That's up to her.
Oh, right. Lianbao told me.
About that fake doctor thing.
Thank you.
Thank me for what?
For helping you hide it from everyone?
Or for dragging my feet and not letting you get treated?
If exposing you would actually do any good,
I'd love to tell the whole world right now
about your lies.
Suit yourself.
If there's nothing else, I'm hanging up.
Bye.
Jing'er.
Mom.
You're... you're back.
Uh...
I'll... I'll go throw this out.
Just put it in the fridge.
Jing'er.
Still mad?
I know.
That...
All these years, I...
Don't say it.
That... me and that Teacher Xiatian...
There's really nothing going on.
I just wanted her
to help promote Penglexuan.
Wang Chunsheng.
You really underestimate me.
Dinner's ready, it's in the pot.
Go ahead and eat.
Feifei.
You haven't changed clothes these past two days, have you?
Didn't your dad wash them for you?
Yeah.
Mom, where did you go this time?
Was it fun?
Did you take any nice photos?
It was okay.
Here.
Later on,
the three of us should go on a trip together.
It's been a long time since we went together.
Then we have to pick a place
that Mom likes to go to.
Right, right, right.
Let's go there.
Okay.
Great!
This... this dish smells amazing.
This...
Smells great.
Scrambled eggs.
Haven't had this in a long time.
You haven't been eating properly these past two days?
Didn't your dad cook for you?
He did.
But it's nowhere near as good as this, right?
Gotta eat three bowls of rice today.
Thanks.
Feifei, come on, have some meat.
Eat some of this meat.
Sir, how many in your party?
I'm waiting for someone.
Manager Dong.
You're exactly the kind of
exceptionally classy woman.
You flatter me, President Luo.
No, no, no, don't be awkward.
Come on, come on.
A toast to you.
Cheers.
President Luo, then we'll consider this matter settled.
I'll send you the contract later.
Sure.
To be honest with you,
the reason I'm willing to work with your company
is because of you.
Thank you, thank you.
You can rest assured.
I certainly won't let you down on my end.
I believe that.
Your watch is off, isn't it?
Come on, let me adjust it for you.
Let me adjust it.
Actually,
I wanted to tell you
I hope our cooperation
can be a bit closer.
You...
Oh, it's already this late.
Sorry, Director Luo.
I have something else to attend to.
I need to head out first.
I've already taken care of the bill.
Is it something urgent?
Yes, I have to pick up my kid from school.
You stay a while longer.
Picking up the kid is important.
Come on, I'll have my driver take you.
No, no, no.
No, I drove myself.
It's fine. If you're leaving,
what's the point of me sitting here alone?
Come on.
Anyway, Qianqian,
we had a pleasant chat today, right?
Yes, very pleasant.
But it feels a bit unfinished.
I'll find a place another time,
and we can have a proper chat, okay?
Where do you think you're putting your hand?
Are you out of your mind?
What? Who the hell are you?
Who am I? I'll smack you!
Li Lianbao!
You...
Are you insane or something?
Don't hold me back!
No...
What are you doing?
What? Didn't you see that jerk had bad intentions?
Who are you calling a jerk?
I'm talking about you!
Look,
there are too many people here.
Let's go somewhere else to talk.
Let's go.
Say whatever you have to say right here.
I think it's necessary
for us to be clearer with each other.
What's unclear between us?
You knew perfectly well I was working, entertaining a client.
You got so worked up just now.
What were you trying to do?
Situations like this will happen a lot in the future.
So, every single time,
are you going to drag the guy out and beat him up?
Or do I have to have you watching me
every time I go out to work from now on?
I know
you've definitely encountered
this kind of thing more than once.
And I believe you have the ability
to handle people like that.
But when I see it, I can't stand it.
I can't bear to see the woman I love
being harassed like that by someone else.
Li Lianbao,
we're both adults.
Don't mix work and feelings together.
Okay?
And I made it perfectly clear to you before.
I don't want our relationship
to get too complicated.
Don't interfere with each other's work and life.
But now it seems
you simply can't do that.
No.
Isn't our relationship simple enough?
I was just acting out of concern and a desire to protect you.
Was I wrong for that?
What are you to me?
Fine.
I overthought it.
I'm sorry.
I have things to do.
Come in.
See, the home really needs you.
It's much more comfortable with you here.
That's a really beautiful dress.
I've never seen this dress before.
I just bought it a couple of days ago.
Close the door and have a seat.
Look at this of mine...
Then this pillow of mine, I'll...
You haven't said a word all day.
For so many days, you've had no news either.
No, it's just... you're like this...
It's a bit scary, you know?
Is it really that scary?
No.
I thought you were going to... you know...
What?
I thought it was to...
...divorce me.
Divorce?
In your dreams.
I'll outlive you, I will.
Um...
Um... I'll put this here.
Put it there.
Actually, I've been thinking these past few days too. Really.
This... this...
This me...
I have my own problems.
And also, the way we've been living...
You know, these twenty-some years...
It's just been a bit too...
Right? Just being together all the time...
It's just... like left hand and right hand.
When other people say that...
I think it's really true.
We just coordinate so well...
But then...
You know, if one were really missing...
Right? It just... it just...
It feels completely lost and helpless.
I've also been thinking these past couple days.
Why did I let myself become...
...so unkempt?
Like an old housewife.
Alright, alright, you don't look like an old housewife at all.
Really.
Starting today...
Even when I sleep...
I have to look pretty.
Right, right, right. Pretty.
And also...
I...
I shouldn't place all my happiness...
...on you and our son.
My happiness should come from myself.
No, there's a bit of a problem with that, you know?
You should place your happiness...
...on us.
And I, I should also place my happiness...
...on you.
But neither of us should...
...place our happiness...
...on that little jerk.
He's about to take the college entrance exam, right?
He'll say "off to college" and be gone.
He'll leave us in the dust then.
He'll have his own life, right?
We should just ignore him.
We'll be happy on our own.
Let me tell you, starting today...
I... I looked up a famous quote, you know?
I think it's absolutely right.
It's about how a wife...
...I should treat like a lover.
Wang Chunsheng, let me tell you...
That Xiao Zhang from your department store...
And that whole string of things before...
You still haven't explained them clearly to me.
Look, look, look.
I bought you this.
This... this...
You always said not to buy you things.
But they say...
...even if you just buy some meat or something...
Take a look.
Stop shaking it around.
Aren't you just wasting money again?
No, you... I think...
How much did this cost?
As a woman...
I believe you deserve to have this in your life.
Come on, come on, let me put it on you.
No, this...
Don't throw this box away later.
Look at the ring, not the box.
No, no.
Don't throw the box away, I'll use it for something else later.
This is really nice.
Yeah, it can even be a night light.
When you get up to use the bathroom or something.
How much was it?
Who cares how much?
I told you not to buy it.
Look at you...
You're always wasting money like this.
You... this, this, this...
No, no.
What do I earn money for?
Isn't it to buy you things?
When I go to work later...
I'll have to take it off.
What if I lose it?
What would we do then?
See, see? You... you're such a...
You just held it together for a little bit...
You're still destined for manual labor, I'm telling you.
This... this must be really expensive, right?
Annoying. Wasting money.
Do you like it?
This... you...
You... you...
Just say you like it, for goodness' sake.
No, I...
I'll even wear it to sleep.
Just don't lose it or anything later.
As long as you like it.
Go to sleep.
Put the pillow down for me.
Who do you think you're ordering around?
Fine, fine, fine. I'll do it myself.
Myself, myself, myself.
Such a hard life.
Hurry up.
Faster.
No, are you going to sleep with it on?
Let's take it off.
You... why do you talk so much?
You get in bed first. Turn off the light.
Get in.
Weiguo: five hundred thousand.
Manager Qiu's deposit commission: one hundred thousand.
Weiguo buying my shares: five hundred thousand.
I still have less than one hundred ninety thousand myself.
It'll work. It'll work.
It'll work.
Alright then.
Great.
From now on...
Dong Qian is our official partner.
We're a family again.
Then let's have a pleasant cooperation from now on.
Pleasant cooperation.
Pleasant.
Good. From now on, it's a partnership.
Big Bro, I've got something else to do.
So I'll head off first.
Leaving?
Uh, see him out.
I'm off, Weiguo.
See him out.
No need, Big Bro.
I'll walk you out.
Really, it's fine.
Why are you two acting so weird?
What nonsense are you talking?
I've got things to do too, I'm off.
Sorry for asking you out on such short notice.
I just suddenly became very interested in some things.
I think you can give me the answers.
The reason you stirred up all that trouble...
...was to take Lianbao's shares...
...in Hive Tech, right?
Or rather...
...the reason you were willing to invest in Pengle Xuan before...
...was for this.
Sorry.
That's a trade secret.
I can't tell you.
I don't know how important this Hive Tech...
...really is to you.
But I'll figure it out soon.
I hope you don't try any tricks.
Martin, you should think first...
...about how to live a little longer.
You worry about yourself first.
Lao Zhang.
I want to make a deal with you.
I can give up all my equity in Rice.
But you have to do me one last favor.
Kevin has invested in many new agricultural companies...
...in Southeast Asia and China these past two years.
And he's been in frequent contact...
...with various countries' agriculture ministries.
Hive is a company that makes entertainment-focused...
...wearable products.
I don't see any connection to agriculture.
Maybe you're overthinking it.
Alright, I'll think about it some more.
Naive.
You...
...don't reply to messages or answer calls.
I thought you were rejecting me again.
I was just on a call.
You finally took the initiative to ask me out.
Because I understood a saying.
"Only the fish knows if the water is warm or cold."
A lot of things in life are probably like that.
He didn't force me...
...to not drink this coffee.
Later, he didn't insist on living...
...his carefree life either.
When two people are together...
...you can't just think about yourself.
You have to consider the other person too.
Right?
So you were convinced by her just like that?
I wouldn't say I was convinced by her.
I figured it out myself.
Some of my own problems.
What problems?
I always say you're self-righteous...
...but actually, the self-righteous one is me.
I thought the onlooker sees most of the game.
But actually, with many things...
...only when you're in the situation yourself...
...do you know what the hardship is like.
Of course...
...it's quite easy to give advice to others.
But actually, I shouldn't have done that.
Of course, I definitely hope...
...you can have the surgery as soon as possible.
It's just that from now on...
...I won't...
...force my ideas onto you.
About that photography exhibition...
...can you help me contact some venues?
If the exhibition makes a profit...
...I can give you a cut.
What about that blond friend of yours?
Xiaoqi?
I don't know his name.
He went home to deal with other things.
Alright?
Alright.
After I finish handling things at the shop...
...I'll help you.
It's settled then.
Deal.
I will.
No going back on your word.
Okay.
The cold cucumber salad for table three is almost ready, right?
Almost ready, almost ready.
You scared me! What are you doing?
I'm busy!
I saw this from way over there...
...it's so shiny!
Really dazzling.
I'm telling you, my hand feels heavy wearing this.
You're just secretly pleased with yourself.
I'm always afraid it'll fall into a dish.
Don't let a customer chew on it.
Food's coming up!
Cucumber salad.
Taking the cucumber salad over.
Thanks for the hard work, really.
What did I come here for?
All the dishes are here.
Big Bro.
If the flavor isn't to your liking, just let me know.
Sis-in-law, everything's okay now?
When was there ever a problem?
Right, your...
...how's that Harvard thing going?
Here we go again.
No, I'm applying for the visa right now.
What are you planning?
I'll go with you!
No, it's such a major surgery...
...and it's a new technology too.
I won't feel at ease if I don't go.
No need, Big Bro.
I'm a grown adult, it's not necessary.
What do you mean 'not necessary'?
Chef!
This plate...
Right, right, right.
Go attend to your work.
Listen to me, I'm telling you...
...we're settling it like this.
You hurry back and get some rest.
We'll talk later, we'll talk.
Don't you 'we'll talk later' me!
Coming, coming!
Plate!
Sis-in-law.
You and Big Bro are okay now?
That's good, really good.
You hurry, hurry back and rest.
You take care and rest.
You're positively glowing.
I'm off.
Get some good rest.
Uncle, I need to talk to you.
Close the door.
Okay.
Go ahead, what is it?
Never mind, you don't have to say it. I know.
You have a crush on someone, right?
Is it a classmate or an online friend?
Neither.
She's just a really pretty girl.
Uncle, when you like someone...
...should you tell her?
That depends.
But first, you need to be sure...
...if she likes you back.
I really can't be sure about that.
Then you should just tell her.
It's always better to say it than not.
So you won't regret it later.
However...
You need to be mentally prepared.
In case she rejects you...
...you have to be able to accept it.
That would be pretty awkward.
Her rejecting me is okay.
As long as she doesn't tell anyone.
Uncle, so...
Based on your experience...
...how should a guy confess to make a girl like it?
You're asking the wrong person.
Do you know why?
Why?
Your Third Uncle never needed to confess.
I get it.
That was back in my youth.
Then I'll go ask my dad.
Don't bother asking him.
He's washed up.
Go check it out.